

# MARK BEAN

Developer

# **PROFILE**

I have had an issue with my health and can no longer drive long distances or do field work in my current profession for the foreseeable future and thus am looking for a change in career.

Before now, programming was "fun" and something to pass the time. I have completed an immense amount of training from Udemy on everything from Python and SQL database classes to full stack web development over the last 5 years. I would put my understanding of object oriented programming at an "intermediate" level, but have never actually had a developer career.

I am well versed in multiple programming languages, have some basic experience debugging code, am great at all things Microsoft, and have lived on a computer since I was 11 years old with my first Windows 95 machine!

My most recent course on Udemy was a React course and I fell even more in love with development using that framework!

## CONTACT

PHONE: 1-513-505-5204

#### WEBSITE:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/markbean-619a70215/

https://github.com/hvacTech0302

**EMAIL:** 

Mb030287@proton.me

# **HOBBIES**

Vacationing with Family Disney Star Wars Continuous learning

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Udemy**

2019 - Present

Lifelong learner dedicated to immersing myself into the web development lifestyle for the rest of my life. Multiple developer courses completed and in progress.

#### **Tennessee College of Applied Technology**

2014 - 2016

HVAC/R Technical Degree focusing on residential and commercial HVAC and appliance repair.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Air Force One Service Manager & BAS Integrator

2021-Present

Manager of the Service Department and liaison to the Building Automation Service Department specializing in programming and starting up programmable logic controllers and Niagara BAS Systems using functional programming and ladder programming.

## **Comfort Solutions Service Technician**

2017-2021

Lead Service Technician in charge of diagnostic service and installation of HVAC equipment

## Ober Gatlinburg Service Technician

2016-2017

Entry Level HVAC service technician responsible for troubleshooting HVAC issues at the site.

#### **SKILLS**

